Guide to the Albert C. Woodroof and A. C. Woodroof, Jr. Papers and Architectural Drawings
Albert C. Woodroof and A. C. Woodroof, Jr. Papers and Architectural Drawings
- Drawings, 1927-1977; 1927 1977
  - A. C. Woodroof Jr. Drawings, 1927-1976; 1927 1976
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: Phase B, East West Mall, 1970 (Tube 97)
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: Winn-Dixie Supermarket, 1967 (Tube 11)
      Air conditioning, mechanical plans
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: Winn-Dixie Supermarket, 1967 (Tube 1)
      Electrical plans
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: Winn-Dixie Supermarket, 1967 (Tube 8)
      Fixture plan, floor plan, elevations, sections, plumbing plan, mechanical plan
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: Winn-Dixie Supermarket, 1967 (Tube 4)
      Foundation plans
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: Winn-Dixie Supermarket, 1967 (Tube 2)
      Plumbing plans, mechanical plans
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: Winn-Dixie Supermarket, 1967-1968 (Tube 23)
      Tabulation of bids, shop plans, structural sections, door details, fixture plan, floor plans
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: Winn-Dixie Supermarket, Eckerd, 1967 (Tube 5)
      Wall sections and details, doors, roof
    - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: Winn-Dixie Supermarket, The Jewel Box, 1967-1970 (Tube 9)
      Electrical plans, floor plans
    - Presbyterian House, 1962-1963 (Tube 58)
      Curtain wall
      Loewenstein-Atkinson Associates, Architects; Greensboro (N.C.)
    - Presbyterian House, 1963 (Tube 60)
      Details
    - Presbyterian House, 1963 (Tube 55)
      Vestibule door, elevations, door frame, details
    - Presbyterian House, 1965 (Flatfolder 16)
    - Presbyterian House, 1965 (Flatfolder 15)
    - Presbyterian House: Campus christian life committee (Tube 177)
    - Professional Village West, 1973 (Tube 142)
      Parking deck, foundation, tax maps, steel construction details
    - Property of Guilford Mills, Inc., 1964 (Tube 157)
      Hollowell, Borum & Associates; Greensboro (N.C.)
    - Proposed nature museum, 1956 (Tube 178)
    - Proximity School for the Road of Education: Cafeteria, 1947 (Tube 89)
    - Redding (Mr. and Mrs. John) residence (Tube 60)
      Austin Ralph J. Jr.; Asheboro (N.C.)
    - Residential development (Tube 59)
      Woodroof, MacRae and Senell Architects; Greensboro (N.C.)
    - Residential development (Tube 60)
      Site plan, site analysis
    - Robert H. Ham Associates, Ltd.: Warehouse addition, 1976 (Tube 72)
      Sections, elevations, floor plans
    - Rockingham County Recreational and Playground Development: Assembly building (Tube 166)
      Leaksville (N.C.)
    - Schenck (Mr. and Mrs. J. S., III) residence (1 of 2), 1966 (Tube 55)
      2306 Princess Ann Street, Greensboro, N.C.
    - Schenck (Mr. and Mrs. J. S., III) residence (2 of 2), 1966 (Tube 177)
    - Servomation Incorporated, 1969 (Tube 185)
    - Stevens (Mr. & Mrs. A. F., Jr.) residence addition, 1957 (Tube 141)
      Floor plan, foundation plan, elevations, details
    - Tangelwood Terrace Apartments (Flatfolder 4)
    - Unidentified drawings (1 of 3) (Flatfolder 8)
    - Unidentified drawings (2 of 3) (Tube 65)
    - Unidentified drawings (3 of 3) (Tube 173)
    - Unidentified drawings (1 of 2) (Tube 174)
    - Unidentified drawings (2 of 2) (Tube 175)
    - Unidentified photos (Flatfolder 6)
    - Unidentified sketches (Tube 58)
    - University of North Carolina at Greensboro, 1968 (Flatfolder 10)
    - University of North Carolina at Greensboro: Library renovation, Rare Books Room, 1973 (Tube 118)
    - University of North Carolina at Greensboro: Library renovation, Rare Books Room, 1973 (Tube 117)
    - University of North Carolina at Greensboro: Library, rare books room entrance, 1974 (Tube 178)
    - University of North Carolina at Greensboro: Phase II library addition, 1971 (Tube 35)
      Cover sheet, site plans, floor plans, finish schedule, elevations, doors
    - University of North Carolina at Greensboro: Phase II library addition, 1971 (Tube 36)
      Elevations, sections, details, toilets, reflected ceiling plans, circulation desk
    - University of North Carolina at Greensboro: Phase II library addition, 1971 (Tube 37)
      Elevator and stair details, floor plans, foundation plan, sections and details, framing plans, column schedule
    - University of North Carolina at Greensboro: Phase II library addition (1 of 2), 1972 (Tube 29)
      Elevations, sections
    - University of North Carolina at Greensboro: Phase II library addition (2 of 2), 1972 (Tube 30)
    - University of North Carolina at Greensboro: Phase II library addition (1 of 2), 1972 (Tube 28)
      Joist details, key plan, anchor layout
    - University of North Carolina at Greensboro: Phase II library addition (2 of 2), 1972 (Tube 31)
    - University of North Carolina at Greensboro: Warehouse and shop, 1968-1969 (Tube 61)
      Site plans, elevations, sections, floor plan
    - Vinje Lutheran Church (Tube 187)
      Willmar (Minn.)
    - Waltham Senior High School (Tube 187)
      Waltham (Mass.)
    - West Ridge Road, 1957 (Tube 148)
      Topography map
    - Winn-Dixie Stores, Inc. (1 of 2), 1970 (Tube 51)
      Guide plans
      Madison (N.C.)
    - Winn-Dixie Stores, Inc. (2 of 2), 1970 (Tube 52)
    - Winn-Dixie Supermarket (1 of 2), 1971 (Tube 47)
    - Winn-Dixie Supermarket (2 of 2), 1971 (Tube 48)
    - Woltz (Mr. and Mrs. J. M., Jr.) garden gate, 1966 (Tube 68)
      510 Woodland Drive, Greensboro, N.C.
    - Wood (Mr. and Mrs. W. A., Jr.) residence, 1966-1967 (Tube 13)
      Floor plans, sections, elevations
      Woodroof and MacRae, Architects, Inc.; Woodroof A. C. (Albert Cecil) Jr. 1920-1991; Pinehurst (N.C.)
    - Wood (Mr. and Mrs. W. A., Jr.) residence, 1966 (Tube 58)
    - Wood (Mr. and Mrs. W. A., Jr.) residence, 1966 (Tube 14)
      Plot plan, elevations, sections, framing plan, floor plans
      Woodroof and MacRae, Architects, Inc.; Pinehurst (N.C.)
    - Wood (Mr. and Mrs. W. A., Jr.) residence, 1967 (Tube 49)
      Elevations, floor plan, specifications
      Pinehurst (N.C.)
    - Wood (Mr. and Mrs. W. A., Jr.) residence, 1967 (Flatfolder 4)
    - Woodroof (Mr. C. E.) residence, 1927 (Flatfolder 3)
      Lynchburg (N.C.)
  - Albert C. Woodroof Drawings, 1929-1986; 1929 1986
    - 833 Jefferson Standard Building (Tube 143)
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Greensboro (N.C.)
    - Agriculture-Vocational Building, 1941 (Tube 158)
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; McLeansville (N.C.)
    - Alamance Presbyterian Church, 1965 (Tube 83)
      Floor plans, site plans
    - Alamance Presbyterian Church, 1965 (Tube 82)
    - Alamance Presbyterian Church: Unit #4 (1 of 2), 1966 (Tube 122)
      Sections, foundations, roofing plan, details, grading plan
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Guilford County (N.C.)
    - Alamance Presbyterian Church: Unit #4 (2 of 2), 1966 (Tube 123)
    - Alamance School, 1946; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986 (Tube 227)
    - Alamance School: Additions, 1953; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986 (Tube 228)
    - Alamance School Building: Alterations and additions, 1936 (Tube 116)
      Basemanet plan, elevations, details
    - American Legion: Alterations to the Headquarters of the Henry K. Burtner Post #35, 1944 (Tube 143)
      Elevations, plans, details
    - Asheboro Street Baptist Church: Addition, 1951-1952; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986 (Tube 199)
    - Balfour School: Alterations and additions (1 of 2), 1945; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986 (Tube 204)
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Asheboro (N.C.)
    - Balfour School: Alterations and additions (2 of 2), 1945; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986 (Tube 205)
    - Bank of Madison: Alterations and additions, 1961 (Tube 111)
      Floor plans, sections, details
      Woodroof A. C. (Albert Cecil) Jr. 1920-1991; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Madison (N.C.)
    - Berny (Mr. G. A.) residence, 1941 (Tube 153)
      Floor plans, elevation, foundation/plot plan, heating layout
    - Bledsoe (Mr. Thomas B.) feed barn, 1937 (Tube 166)
    - Boren (G. Simpson) residence, 1943 (Tube 154)
    - Boren (Mrs. C. P.) store building, 1941 (Tube 165)
    - Boyd (Mr. Chas T.) residence, 1938 (Tube 141)
    - Boyd (Mr. Chas T.) residence heating, 1938 (Tube 118)
    - Brawley (J. W.) residence, 1961 (Tube 153)
      Entrance hood details
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Woodroof A. C. (Albert Cecil) Jr. 1920-1991; Greensboro (N.C.)
    - Brooks (Mr. A. L.) panelling of office, 1945 (Tube 166)
    - Brower Township School Building, 1938 (Tube 158)
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Randolph County (N.C.)
    - Carlson (Dr. C. I.) beach house, 1948 (Tube 86)
      Floor plans, elevations, sections
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; New Hanover County (N.C.)
    - Carlson (Dr. C. I.) beach house, 1947 (Tube 154)
      Floor plans, elevations, cross sections
    - Carolina by Products Company: Office building, 1944 (Tube 143)
      Elevations, cross sections, floor plans
    - Causey (Mr. Frank R.) residence, 1950 (Tube 120)
      Details, sections, elevations, foundation plans
    - Centenary Methodist Church, Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986 (Tube 226)
    - Centenary Methodist Church, 1959 (Tube 152)
      First floor plan
    - Centenary Methodist Church (1 of 2), 1960; Woodroof A. C. (Albert Cecil) Jr. 1920-1991; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986 (Tube 214)
      Woodroof A. C. (Albert Cecil) Jr. 1920-1991; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Greensboro (N.C.)
    - Centenary Methodist Church (2 of 2), 1960; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Woodroof A. C. (Albert Cecil) Jr. 1920-1991 (Tube 215)
    - Centenary Methodist Church, 1968; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986 (Tube 225)
    - Check (Mr. and Mrs. Charles) porch enclosure, 1986 (Tube 152)
    - City of Greensboro: Fire station (Tube 136)
      Cornice details
    - City of Greensboro: Topographic maps (Tube 238)
    - Cockman (D.) alterations, 1942 (Tube 165)
      904 Spring Garden Street
    - Coleridge School Building: Addition, 1938 (Tube 158)
    - Colfax School: Agriculture-Vocational addition, 1942 (Tube 158)
    - College Park Methodist Church, 1939 (Tube 161)
      Elevations, floor plans, construction details, heating layout
    - College Park Methodist Church, 1952 (Tube 160)
    - College Place Methodist Church: Addition, Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986
    - College Place Methodist Church: Addition, 1953-1955; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986 (Tube 212)
    - College Place Methodist Church: Alterations, 1956 (Tube 159)
    - College Place Methodist Church: Alterations, 1956 (Tube 124)
      Floor plans, heating plan
    - Crews Methodist Church, 1944 (Tube 159)
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Forsyth County (N.C.)
    - Crews Methodist Church, 1944 (Tube 124)
      Section, floor plans, cupola details
    - Crutchfield (Mr. J. M.) residence, 1939 (Tube 128)
      Foundation plan, floor plan, elevations, sections
    - Davis Street Methodist Church (1 of 2), 1949-1950; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986 (Tube 200)
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Burlington (N.C.)
    - Davis Street Methodist Church (2 of 2), 1949-1950; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986 (Tube 201)
    - Dillard Paper Co.: Warehouse, 1947 (Tube 166)
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Charlotte (N.C.)
    - Dillard Paper Company, 1947 (Tube 167)
    - Dwellings for a development, 1946 (Tube 139)
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986
    - Ellington (Mr. A. G.) garage building alterations and addition, 1937 (Tube 165)
    - Elon College Community Church, 1958; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Woodroof A. C. (Albert Cecil) Jr. 1920-1991 (Tube 203)
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Woodroof A. C. (Albert Cecil) Jr. 1920-1991; Elon College (N.C.)
    - Factory Building Extension, 1933 (Tube 165)
    - First Baptist Church (Flatfolder 12)
    - First Baptist Church, 1944 (Flatfolder 5)
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Eggers & Higgins; Greensboro (N.C.)
    - First Baptist Church, 1953 (Tube 110)
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Monroe (N.C.)
    - First Baptist Church, 1964 (Tube 156)
      Shelter, space analysis of the religious education building, bookshelving for library study
    - First Church of Christ Scientist, 1963 (Flatfolder 5)
    - First Church of Christ Scientist, 1963 (Tube 155)
    - First Citizens Bank: Alterations, 1962 (Tube 155)
      Elevations, floor plans
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Woodroof A. C. (Albert Cecil) Jr. 1920-1991; Hickory (N.C.)
    - First Evangelical and Reformed Church (1 of 2), 1956; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986 (Tube 218)
    - First Evangelical and Reformed Church (2 of 2), 1956; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986 (Tube 219)
    - First Evangelical and Reformed Church, 1956 (Tube 147)
      Cupola details, framing, section details
    - First Evangelical and Reformed Church: Building, 1954 (Tube 152)
    - First Methodist Episcopal Church: Addition, 1938 (Tube 124)
    - First Presbyterian Apartment Building, 1961 (Tube 58)
      Stair details
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Woodroof A. C. (Albert Cecil) Jr. 1920-1991
    - First Presbyterian Church, 1953; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986 (Tube 217)
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; High Point (N.C.)
    - First Presbyterian Church, 1961; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Woodroof A. C. (Albert Cecil) Jr. 1920-1991 (Tube 216)
    - First Presbyterian Church, 1957 (Tube 84)
      Floor plans, plot plans, alterations
    - First Presbyterian Church, 1957 (Tube 83)
    - First Presbyterian Church: Addition, 1951-1953; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986 (Tube 202)
    - First Presbyterian Church: Addition (1 of 2), 1952-1953; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986 (Tube 195)
    - First Presbyterian Church: Addition (2 of 2), 1952-1953; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986 (Tube 196)
    - First Presbyterian Church: Alterations to the boiler room and Smith Building, 1961 (Tube 79)
    - First Presbyterian Church: Children's education building, 1961 (Tube 109)
      Foundation plans, roof framing, truss elevations
    - First Southern Company: Office building (1 of 2), 1960 (Tube 126)
      Floor plans, details, sections
    - First Southern Company: Office building (2 of 2), 1960 (Tube 134)
    - First Southern Company: Office building, 1960 (Tube 155)
      Floor plans, schedules
    - First Southern Company: Office building, 1960 (Tube 112)
    - Forbis & Murray: Porch for the office entrance, 1943 (Tube 165)
    - Four Room Brick Tenant House for the Sapona Cotton Mills, Inc., 1937 (Tube 143)
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Cedar Falls (N.C.)
    - Franklin Heights Methodist Church, 1946 (Tube 124)
      Elevations, constructions, details, sections
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Mount Airy (N.C.)
    - Gate City Tire Company: Proposed building, 1945 (Tube 165)
    - Gate City Tire Company: Tire Service Building, 1945 (Tube 85)
    - Glascock Stove & Manufacturing Co., 1940 (Tube 172)
    - Glascock Stove & Manufacturing Co.: Offices for the Shipping Department, 1944 (Tube 165)
    - Glen Raven Cotton Mills: Recreation building (Tube 165)
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Morehead City (N.C.)
    - Greensboro College: Alterations to the Administration Building, attic stair enclosure for west stairway of Main Building, 1942 (Tube 158)
    - Greensboro Country Club, 1959 (Tube 103)
    - Greensboro Country Club, 1961 (Tube 146)
      Layout of tennis courts, pool layout
    - Greensboro Junior Museum, 1962 (Tube 91)
      Plot plan, details, alternatives
    - Greensboro Junior Museum: Proposed Planetarium, 1960 (Tube 168)
      Scheme B
    - Greensboro-High Point Airport: Terminal building (1 of 4), 1957; Voorhees & Everhart Associates; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986 (Tube 223)
      Voorhees & Everhart Associates; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Guilford County (N.C.)
    - Greensboro-High Point Airport: Terminal building (2 of 4), 1957; Voorhees & Everhart Associates; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986 (Tube 209)
    - Greensboro-High Point Airport: Terminal building (3 of 4), 1957; Voorhees & Everhart Associates; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986 (Tube 210)
    - Greensboro-High Point Airport: Terminal building (4 of 4), 1957; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Voorhees & Everhart Associates (Tube 224)
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Voorhees & Everhart Associates; Guilford County (N.C.)
    - Greensboro Memorial Coliseum, 1947; McKinn & Norfleet; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986 (Tube 222)
      McKinn & Norfleet; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Greensboro (N.C.)
    - Griffin (Harvey L.) apartment building, 1937 (Tube 166)
    - Guilford College auditorium (1 of 2), 1960; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986 (Tube 236)
    - Guilford College auditorium (2 of 2), 1960; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986 (Tube 237)
    - Guilford College auditorium: Additions and alternate chapel design, 1961-1965 (Tube 115)
    - Guilford College High School: Addition, 1938 (Tube 158)
    - Guilford College: Chapel-Auditorium building, 1957 (Tube 150)
    - Guilford College: Founders Hall alterations and additions, 1955 (Tube 125)
      Electrical, foundation plans, details, sections
    - Guilford College: Founders Hall alterations and additions, 1955 (Tube 112)
    - Guilford College: Gymnasium, 1939 (Tube 152)
      Brusselle Alfred; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Greensboro (N.C.)
    - Guilford College: Gymnasium, 1940 (Tube 88)
    - Guilford College: Larger campus plan of arrangement, 1939 (Flatfolder 17)
      Harris Hugh; Guilford County (N.C.)
    - Guilford College: President's residence (Tube 117)
      Floor plans, foundation plan, elevations
    - Guilford College: Residence hall for men, 1956 (Tube 147)
    - Guilford College: Residence hall for women, 1946 (Tube 154)
      Floor plans, sections, elevations, plot plan, details, structural diagrams, heating layout
    - Guilford College: Science Hall and women's dormitory elevation photostats (Flatfolder 11)
    - Guilford College: Student Union, 1955 (Tube 150)
    - Guilford College: Student Union, 1955 (Tube 151)
      Heating plan
    - Guilford County Board of Education: Summer and Alamance Schools, Cannery building, 1944 (Tube 159)
    - Guilford County Tuberculosis Sanatorium: Living quarters for negro employees, 1944 (Tube 133)
      Floor plan, foundation plan
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Jamestown (N.C.)
    - Guilford High School: Addition, 1963; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986 (Tube 193)
    - Guilford Mills, Inc.: Office addition, 1965 (Tube 109)
      Foundation plans, elevations, sections
    - Guilford Mills, Inc.: Warehouse addition, 1965 (Tube 99)
    - Haile (Mr. Frank H.) residence, 1941 (Tube 145)
      Heating layout, floor plan, sections, elevations
    - Hall (Mr. Russell F.) residence, 1951; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986 (Tube 233)
    - Hall (Mr. Russell F.) residence: Alterations and additions, 1939 (Flatfolder 3)
    - Home Savings and Loan Associates, 1956 (Tube 127)
      Plot plans, sections, details
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Leaksville (N.C.)
    - Home Savings and Loan Associates, 1956 (Tube 118)
    - John W. Woody School Building: Restoration and alteration, 1937 (Tube 158)
    - Jordan (Mr. Glen R.) residence, 1940 (Tube 145)
      Foundation plan, floor plan, elevations, wall sections
    - Joseph Hewes Hotel Building for the U.S.O.: Alterations, 1943 (Tube 144)
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Edenton (N.C.)
    - Junior High School for Negroes: Addition, 1948; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986 (Tube 206)
    - Junior High School for Negroes: Addition, 1948; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986 (Tube 207)
    - Junior High School for Negroes: Addition, 1948-1954 (Tube 162)
      Construction details, plot plan, framing/footing plan, floor plans, elevations, sections
    - Justice Drug Company: Freight elevator shaft and penthouse in the existing building, 1946 (Tube 133)
      Elevations, sections, floor plans
    - Kistler (Dr. L. D.) residence, 1934 (Tube 138)
      Floor plans, elevations, sections, construction details
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Randleman (N.C.)
    - Kriegsman's, Inc.: Store room alteration, 1943 (Tube 143)
    - Lambert (Mr. and Mrs. D. H.) residence, 1950 (Flatfolder 3)
    - Lambert (Mr. D. H.) and Stout (F. R.) double store building, 1939 (Tube 133)
      Half elevations, sections, floor plans
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Elkin (N.C.)
    - Lane's Laundry: Addition, 1944 (Tube 143)
      Floor plans, elevations, sections, window details
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; West Market St. (Greensboro, N.C.)
    - Lefkowitz (Mr. A.) store building alterations, 1937 (Tube 143)
    - Lighting fixture drawing (Flatfolder 13)
    - Lindley (Mr. F. H.) residence, 1938 (Tube 149)
    - Ljung (Mr. H. A.) residence, 1941 (Flatfolder 3)
    - Long Memorial Methodist Church: Addition (1 of 2), 1953; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986 (Tube 193)
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Roxboro (N.C.)
    - Long Memorial Methodist Church: Addition (2 of 2), 1953; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986 (Tube 194)
    - Lutheran Church of Our Father, 1962 (Tube 164)
      Chapel design, parish house
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Loewenstein-Atkinson Associates, Architects; Greensboro (N.C.)
    - MacFadyen (Miss Miriam) duplex house, 1939 (Tube 128)
      Foundation plan, floor plans, elevation
    - Madison Building & Loan Association, 1960 (Tube 156)
      Floor plans, elevations, construction details
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Woodroof A. C. (Albert Cecil) Jr. 1920-1991; Madison (N.C.)
    - Madison Building & Loan Association, 1960 (Tube 157)
    - Manor for Sedgefield Inn Co.: Alterations, 1941 (Tube 166)
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Sedgefield (N.C.)
    - Marks (Mr. Benjamin) store front, 1936 (Tube 166)
    - Massachusetts Mutual Life Insurance Co.: Store building alteration, 1937 (Tube 165)
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Springfield (Mass.)
    - Massachussets Mutual Life Insurance Company, 1937 (Tube 167)
      Front entrance details of a store building
    - McCrary (Mr. & Mrs. Charles W.) residence, 1938 (Tube 149)
      Alterations and additions
    - McCrary, (Mr. Charles W.) residence, sleeping porch addition, 1935 (Tube 138)
    - McLeansville Public School: Home Economics building, 1937 (Tube 116)
      Foundation plans, elevations
    - Memorial Baptist Church, 1969 (Tube 121)
      Floor plans, sections, schedule
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Greenville (N.C.)
    - Meyers Department Store: Store front, 1939 (Tube 165)
    - Miller-Jones Co.: Store, 1939 (Tube 165)
    - Miscellaneous specifications (Tube 238)
    - Mitchell (Mr. J. Elwood) residence, 1939 (Tube 140)
    - Mitchell (Mr. J. Elwood) residence, 1939 (Tube 139)
      Orifice heating system
    - Monarch Elevator & Machine Co.: Office and warehouse building, 1944 (Tube 143)
    - Moore & Turner residence, 1935 (Tube 140)
      Entrance details
    - Moore & Turner residence, 1935 (Tube 137)
    - Mt. Zion Evangelical and Reformed Christ: Educational building, 1957 (Tube 102)
      Plans, sections, elevations, framing
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Woodroof A. C. (Albert Cecil) Jr. 1920-1991; China Grove (N.C.)
    - Municipal Building, 1937 (Tube 166)
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Ashe County (N.C.)
    - Narthex of the First Baptist Church, 1957 (Tube 85)
      Registery Desk
    - Nathanael Greene School, 1939 (Tube 135)
      Sections, elevations, floor plan, roof plan
    - National Olympic Church Inc.: The Olympic 350 (Flatfolder 7)
    - New Sharon Methodist Church, 1946 (Tube 124)
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Orange County (N.C.)
    - New Sharon Methodist Church, 1964 (Tube 84)
      Elevations
    - North Carolina Agriculture and Technical College (1 of 2), 1948; McKinn & Norfleet; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986 (Tube 221)
    - North Carolina Agriculture and Technical College (2 of 2), 1948; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; McKinn & Norfleet (Tube 220)